JUAN C. BARRIOS S.

FRONT END DEVELOPER

SKILLS PROFESSIONALS

JavaScript
TypeScript
React
Next
Node
Flutter
React Native

SKILLS PERSONALS

Creative
Trustworthy and professional
Organized
Time management
Teamwork
Fast learner
Motivated

CONTACT

+58 4121556808 juanbarrios045@gmail.com https://juanbs.com/

REFERENCES

JUNIOR SÁNCHEZ

Developer FullStack jysa65.dev@gmail.com

MOISÉS DE LA CRUZ

Backend Developer and DevOps moiseslacruz16@gmail.com

LENNON PEREZ

Front End Developer lenonart14@gmail.com

PROFILE

My name is Juan, I'm 23 years old and I'm from Venezuela. I am a big fan of web development and technology. I am passionate about working as a Front End Developer and I always make sure that what I develop is perfect. I am great at working in a team and I adjust to everything you need.

I'm a Front End Developer with more than five year of work experience.



EXPERIENCE

MONOMA

March 2024 - July 2024

ASP CONSULTING

May 2023 - March 2024

TAUROS

Nov 2019 - Feb 2023

FREELANCER

Sep 2019 - Present

EDUCATION

SYSTEMS ANALYST

Instituto Universitario de Tecnología para la informatica | 2017 - 2020